http://www.webflyer.com/help/privacy.php

(Other sites and services
brought to you by WebFlyer)
FlyerTalk
FlyerTalk Live!
Summary
Because protecting your privacy is very important to WebFlyer, we have adopted the following policies to safeguard your personal information and are committed to protecting its confidentiality. We will limit the collection and use of personal information or "Individual Information" (as defined below) to what is necessary to administer our business, provide you with
the highest quality service, and offer you opportunities we think will be of
interest. We will NOT disclose any Individual Information except in limited circumstances as specifically provided below.
Individual Information means any information, data or records which relate to your use of WebFlyer. There are three types of Individual Information: (1)
"Member Identity and Billing Information," such as your name, street address, telephone number and billing information, and any screen names associated with
your account; (2) "Navigational and Transactional Information," such as
information about where you go or what you buy on WebFlyer; and (3) "Private
Communications Content," such as the contents of email, or private chat room or instant message communications.
Please be aware that WebFlyer is on the Internet. Internet areas may appear to be seamlessly incorporated into WebFlyer and you should be aware that occasionally you will be outside of WebFlyer. When this happens we will make every attempt to identify those areas for you.
Some of the areas that you visit on WebFlyer are operated by companies that are independent from WebFlyer While WebFlyer will seek to require these independent companies (e.g. information providers, advertisers, and merchants) to adhere to our strong privacy principles, WebFlyer does not bear responsibility for their policies or actions. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (such as your real email address) in public areas (e.g., FlyerTalk), your information can be collected and used by others who see it online.
WebFlyer actively participates in industry associations and community groups to support strong and effective privacy guidelines and practices. In fact, we were one of a handful of sites who were picked to test the original privacy policies of Trust-E.
Collection and Storage
(i) Identity and Billing Information
We maintain the following types of Identity and Billing Information when you order products directly from WebFlyer: your name, street address, telephone numbers and payment information. We may also keep information on your communications with our Customer Service department such as written complaints relating to WebFlyer.
(ii) Navigational Information
We may collect and store certain Navigational Information, such as data on the choices you make among the range of available content or merchandise and the times and ways you access WebFlyer.
(iii) Private Communications Content
The email system serving WebFlyer retains the contents of private email communications for a limited period only. Once read, most email is permanently deleted from the system.
Email to and from customers who have purchased consumer products advertised on WebFlyer is removed from the system but may be added to the system managing the customer's record of purchase history. Although this specific rule of retention is the general policy, it is no guarantee that such forms of correspondence will or will not be retained. Consequently, if you wish to keep copies of any communications, you should store such communications on your personal computer hard drive or in print form.
Use
WebFlyer safeguards its Individual Information from unauthorized access and only authorized employees or agents who need to carry out legitimate business functions are permitted access to Individual Information. Employees who violate WebFlyer Inc.s privacy policies are subject to disciplinary actions, including termination where appropriate.
You acknowledge that private communications directed at a person or entity, including WebFlyer Inc., may be used or disclosed by the intended recipient(s) without restrictions relating to privacy or confidentiality.
(i) Identity and Billing
WebFlyer uses Identity and Billing Information to administer our business, ensure that you are properly taken care of as a customer and offer you opportunities that may be of interest.
(ii) Navigational and Transactional Information
WebFlyer uses Navigational and Transactional Information to personalize WebFlyer and for programming and editorial research. For example, we use Navigational and Transactional
Information to understand visitors reactions to design items, content, services
and merchandise offered through WebFlyer and to customize WebFlyer based on the interests of our visitors.
(iii) Private Communications Content
WebFlyer treats private communications on or through WebFlyer as strictly confidential and does not access, use or disclose the contents of private communications, except in limited circumstances.
Disclosure
Because WebFlyer considers the Individual Information we maintain to be confidential, our policy is to not disclose Individual Information to third parties without prior consent (which may be oral or electronic), or unless specifically provided below. WebFlyer reserves the right to use agents, who are bound by strict confidentiality guidelines, to perform storage and processing functions.
(i) Identity and Billing Information
We never make our email list available to companies. All email blasts come directly from us. WebFlyer does not release members telephone numbers, credit card numbers or checking account numbers (or other Individual Information, such as Navigational or Transactional Information or Private Communications Content).
It is our policy not to disclose to third parties Identity information that links a visitors screen name(s) with a visitors actual name, unless required to do so by law or legal process served on WebFlyer (e.g. subpoena). WebFlyer reserves the right to make exceptions to this policy in exceptional circumstances (such as a bomb or suicide threat, or instances of suspected illegal activity) on a case-by-case basis and at WebFlyer Inc.s sole discretion.
WebFlyer intends to abide by applicable laws governing the disclosure to governmental entities of Individual Information and other records. When responding to legal process served on WebFlyer by non-government entities, unless otherwise ordered, WebFlyer's current policy is to make reasonable efforts to notify affected visitor(s) in advance of releasing the information in order to provide visitor(s) an opportunity to pursue any available legal protection.
(ii) Navigational and Transactional Information
WebFlyer will not disclose to third parties Navigational or Transactional Information (e.g. where you go or what you buy through WebFlyer), except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process (e.g., search warrant or court order).
(iii) Private Communications Content
WebFlyer does not access or disclose the contents of private communications (e.g., email), unless it in good faith believes that such action is necessary (a) to comply with applicable law or valid legal process (e.g., search warrant or court order), (b) to protect the rights or property of WebFlyer, or (c) in emergencies when WebFlyer believes that physical safety is at risk. WebFlyer reserves the right to treat as public, any FlyerTalk session which is published or becomes generally known or available.
We hope that this Privacy Policy is one that has been developed in the best interest of our visitors. Should you have any comments or concern regarding anything mentioned above, I'd like to hear from you. WebFlyer is part of the company that brings you Inside Flyer magazine and has been serving frequent flyers since 1986. All during this time we have valued our relationship with our customers and it is our every concern to continue to do business in this manner.
You may reach me at randy@insideflyer.com. If you feel that a phone call might be in order, please call me at (719) 597-8889.
Randy Petersen
President, Frequent Flyer Services
^top
About Us | Advertising | Contact Us | Copyright | Help | Privacy Policy | Products | Legal						A Frequent Flyer Network site. All rights reserved.
